The cat is sleeping.
He had changed a lot, Camus.
These linguists, they are all fadas.
They are all fadas, these linguists.
Of course, you enjoyed drinking it,
that coffee you warmed up.
She, I know her.
I know her, she.
Paul, I talk to him often.
I talk to him often, Paul.
France, I believe in it.
France, I believe in it very much, will succeed.
The neuronal translation is impressive.
The neuronal translation, it's true, is impressive.
In Amsterdam, I went there often.
I went to Amsterdam often.
To me too, she talks to me.
Let her dance. She'll do it all her life.
She will dance all her life.
Free, I am almost never.
Free, I'm almost never.
Sublime, he was.
He was sublime.
Comedian, he will always be.
He was still a comedian.
I stayed there for a long time.
Do you know what he's doing in there?
Julie, I often speak of his success.
Jomski, I often speak of him in my classes.
Clase, his socks disappeared.
This team, the amateurs often suffered because of it.
Paul, Pierre fought with this idiot.
Plastique Bertrand, I have all the records of this madman.
We saw thousands of statues' eyes.
I wrote one of the letters.
That I find another one of watches.
Reading, that's important.
Speed, it's beyond.
A child is precious and fragile.
It moves a lot, a child.
It works hard, a medical student.
It takes all its energy, this kind of work.
Books, Jean, I know she stole a lot from him.
I gave the book to Luc.
He knew it was heavy to carry.
Paul, Marie told him this story well.
Marie told Paul this story well.
I know where Paul went.
I asked these apples who he was going to sell them to.
I asked these apples where he found them.