The cat is sleeping.
Camus had changed a lot.
These linguists, they are all lazy.
Of course, it was a pleasure for you to drink the coffee the cat made you warm.
She, I know her.
Paul, I talk to him often.
France, I believe in her.
France, I believe in her very strongly, will succeed.
The neural translation is impressive.
I went to Amsterdam often.
She talks to me too.
Dance, she will do it all her life.
Free, I am almost never.
Sublime, he was.
Actor, he will always remain.
He was still an actor.
I stayed there for a long time.
In there, do you know what he does?
Julie, I often talk about his success.
James Key, I often talk about him in my classes.
His socks disappeared.
This team, amateurs often suffered because of her.
Paul, Pierre fought with this idiot.
Plastic Bertrand, I have all the records of this fool.
Statue's eyes, we have seen thousands of them.
I wrote one of them.
I still find one of them.
Reading, this is important.
Speed is beyond.
A child is precious and fragile.
A child moves a lot.
He works hard in medicine.
It takes all his energy, this kind of work.
Books, I know she stole a lot.
I gave him the book to Luc.
He knew she was heavy to carry.
Paul, this story, Marie told him well.
This story, Paul, Marie told him well.
I know where Paul went.
I took this apple, to whom he wanted to sell them.
I took this apple, where he found them.