the cat he sleeps the cat he slept the cat he slept the cat he had changed a lot Camus
I had a lot of change Camus, these linguists are all Fada, these linguists are all Fada,
they are all Fada these linguists, they are all Fada these linguists, of course it is
pleasant to drink what the cafe you have heated, of course it is pleasant to drink what
cafe you have heated, I know her, I know her, I know her, I know her, I know her,
Paul, I often talk to him, Paul I often talk to him, Paul, I often talk to him, Paul,
I believe in France, I believe in France, I believe very strongly, we will succeed. The
neuronal translation is impressive, the neuronal translation is true, it is impressive.
Amsterdam, I went often. Amsterdam, I went often. I went often to Amsterdam. I went often to
Amsterdam. Me too, she speaks to me, she speaks to me too. Dancing, she will do it all her life,
she will be dancing all her life in seu c'est, she will dance all her life in seu c'est, she will be dancing all her life in seu c'est.
Free, I do not follow it even a little bit, free I do not follow it even a little bit,
released I do not follow it even a little bit, sublime he was, sublime he was,
he was, sublime he was, sublimes he was, sublimes comedian he will never
remain, comedian he will never remain, he was still a comedian, he was still a
comedian, he was still a comedian, I stayed there for a long time, I
stayed there for a long time, you know what he does, you know what he does, I
say I talk often about his success, I speak often about his success, I
speak of him in my classes, I speak often about him in my classes, classes
7th grade were disappeared, 7th grade were disappeared, this team, the amateurs often suffered
because of it, Paul, Pierre fought with this idiot,
Paul, Pierre fought with this idiot, Plastic Bertrand, I have all the records of this
farfellu, Plastic Bertrand, I have all the records of this farfellu, the eyes of statuettes in the
view of thousands, the eyes of statuettes we saw in the middle, we saw thousands of
eyes of statuettes, we saw thousands of views of statuettes, I wrote one letter, I wrote one
letter that I still find one to show, that I still find one to show, reading,
this is important, reading is important, speed is over, speed is over,
a child is precious and fragile, a child is precious and fragile, it moves a lot,
a child, it moves a lot, a child, it works hard, a medicine student, it works hard
a medicine student, it takes all its energy, this kind of work, it takes all its energy,
this kind of work,
books, I know well that she stole a lot of books, I know well that she stole a lot, I
gave her the book to Luc, I gave him the book to Luc, she knew well that she was
afraid of bringing the suitcase, she knew well that she was afraid of taking the suitcase,
Paul, this story Marie told him well, this story Marie told him well, this story
Paul told him well, this story Paul told him well, I know where Paul went,
I knew where Paul went, I know where Paul went, I know Paul where he went, I asked
these people who had the intention to sell them I asked these people
who had the intent to sell them, I asked them who these people were.
intended to sell them, I asked them who these people were.
he had the intent to sell them, I asked them these people where they
had found them. I asked these people where they had found them.