The dog, he sleeps, the dog sleeps, he sleeps the dog, he sleeps the dog, he had a lot of change
in the truck, he had a lot of change in the truck, it's an English, they are all
learn it from each other.
They learn it from each other.
That's all the time.
Everything is a mystery.
That's it for sure.
They have made you happy to drink what you paid for.
Of course, that will make you happy to drink what you bought for.
She, I know her.
She knows her.
I know her.
Paul, I often speak to him.
I often speak to him.
France, I believe.
France, I believe very strong, will succeed.
The neuronal translation is impressive.
The neuronal translation is true.
It's impressive.
Amsterdam, I often go to them.
I often go to them.
Me too, she speaks to me.
In them, she will do all her life.
She will dance all her life.
She will do all her life.
I will never be able to sleep.
Sublime, it was.
As a means, she will always stay.
She was still as a means.
I stayed for a long time, there.
In her, she knew what she did.
She is like me, I always talk about Herholy.
I speaky face d'ess dislikes when she is sitting.
I am a spoon, often because of her.
I speaky face d'ess Watching her,
watching her.
This is watching sister of my animals.
Watchd her, this is watching sister of my animals.
Paul fell his shoes with this d'oeuf.
I have all the sights of this fafule.
The sights of this fafule.
The statue eyes we saw by his拚.
The eyes of the statue we saw by him.
We saw by his拚, eyes of the statue.
I have written one letter.
That I still find one more to show.
I have written one more to show.
The reading is important.
Evidence is passed.
A child is precious and fragile.
It moves a lot, a child.
A work force, a medicine study.
It takes all its energy, this kind of work.
The books I know well that they stole a lot.
I gave him the book.
It was good that he was able to wear a veil.
It was hard to wear a veil.
Apple, this story Marie told him well.
This story Marie told him well.
I know Paul is come.
I know Paul is coming.
I know he's coming.
I don't know he's coming.
I asked these people to know the idea of the sale.
I asked him these folks to know the idea of the sale.
Who did they request this woman?
This is not him.
He asked晗 Child.
He asked these folks to know the idea of the sale.
I asked him these folks to know the idea of the sale.