The cat is sleeping.
He had changed a lot, Camus.
These linguists, they are all fadas.
They are all fadas, these linguists.
Of course it made you happy to drink it,
the coffee you warmed up.
I know her.
Paul, I talk to him often.
I talk to him often, Paul.
France, I believe in it.
France, I believe in it very much, will succeed.
The neuronal translation is impressive.
The neuronal translation, it's true, is impressive.
In Amsterdam, I went there often.
I went to Amsterdam often.
She talks to me too.
She'll dance all of her life.
Free, I am almost never.
Sublime, he was sublime.
It was sublime.
Actor, he will always be.
He was still an actor.
I stayed there for a long time.
In there, do you know what he's doing?
Julie, I often talk about his success.
Chomsky, I often talk about him in my lessons.
Classic, his socks went missing.
This team, amateurs have often suffered because of it.
Paul, Pierre fought with this idiot.
Plastique Bertrand, I have all the records of this madman.
We saw thousands of statues' eyes.
I wrote one of the letters.
I still find one of them as a watch.
Reading, that's important.
Speed, that's over the top.
A child is precious and fragile.
It moves a child a lot.
It's a lot of work, studying medicine.
It takes all your energy, this kind of work.
Books, Jean, I know she stole a lot of them.
I gave the book to Luc.
He knew she was carrying the suitcase.
Paul, Marie told him this story well.
I know where Paul went.
I asked him who he meant to sell these apples to.
I asked him where he found these apples.